

College Park, MD

💌 caleb.stewart94@gmail.com | 🖸 calebstewart | 🤝 caleb.stewart | 🛅 calebjstewart | 💆 calebjstewart

Summary_

Software Engineering and Cyber Security Expert with Electrical Engineering background. More than 10 years software development expertience in many languages from x86 and ARM Assembly to Python. Experience in SOC, Incident Response and Red Team roles. Passion for building elegant tools and frameworks to automate and simplify operations.

Work Experience

DoD Cyber Protection Team

Fort Meade, MD

SUPPORT ELEMENT TECHNICAL LEAD

Jun 2020 - Present

- Developed and deployed software and hardware load-out for deployable incident response teams.
- · Developed incident response scenarios to provide analyst training and improve mission effectiveness.
- · Qualified Mission Commander and Host Analyst.

Coast Guard Cyber Protection Team

Washington, DC

MISSION ELEMENT LEAD

Feb 2019 - Jun 2020

- · First responder for numerous network security incidents threatening National Critical Infrastructure
- Developed SOP and training requirements for incoming personnel.
- Procured, configured and deployed state of the art incident response hardware platform.

Coast Guard Security Operations Center

Washington, DC

INFRASTRUCTURE SUPPORT BRANCH LEAD

Nov 2017 - Nov 2018

- · Operation and Maintenance of all network defence infrastructure including Intrusion Prevention and Detection Systems, Data-Loss Prevention, Web Content Filter, and Firewalls.
- · Battle Watch Captain supervising security and operational control over all IT systems across the Coast Guard.

Coast Guard Cutter Bertholf

Alameda CA

COMBAT INFORMATION CENTER OFFICER

May 2016 - Nov 2017

- · Responsible for combat and communications equiment and operational planning.
- · Assistant Command Security Officer managed physical, information and operational security programs for entire crew.

National Security Agency

Fort Meade, MD

INTERNSHIP

- · Applied systems-programming expertise to reverse engineer unknown software and catalog all code-paths for further analysis.
- Performed static and dynamic analysis on malware to identify and report all observed activity.

Certifications

Dec 2018 Offensive Security Certified Professional (OSCP), Certification ID: OS-101-017541	Offensive Security
Oct 2020 Exploit Researcher and Advanced Penetration Tester (GXPN), Certification ID: 9192230	GIAC
Dec 2019 Offensive Security Certified Expert (OSCE), Certification ID: OS-CTP-11344	Offensive Security
Feb 2020 Offensive Security Web Expert (OSWE), Certification ID: OS-AWAE-02880	Offensive Security
Mar 2020 Certified Professional Penetration Tester (eCPPT), Certification ID: 9831814	eLearnSecurity
Feb 2020 Offensive Security Wireless Professional (OSWP), Certification ID: OS-BWA-036075	Offensive Security
Dec 2018 Certified Information Systems Security Professional (CISSP), Certification ID: 703304	ISC2

Notable Projects

pwncat

github.com/calebstewart/pwncat

CREATOR

Python, C, C#

Full featured agentless C2 platform built on top of a basic shell providing stable interactive sessions as well as an extensive pluggable API for automated enumeration, persistence, privilege escalation, and report generation.

JANUARY 22, 2021 CALEB STEWART · RÉSUMÉ Katana

github.com/johnhammond/katana

CO-CREATOR Python

Automated Capture the Flag (CTF) problem solver. Implements a multi-threaded problem identification and solution framework capable of automatically solving cyber security challenges from a variety of categories.

CTF4Hire github.com/ctf4hire

LEAD SYSTEM ENGINEER, CHALLENGE DEVELOPER

Python, Kubernetes, C, Assembly, GKE

Designed and implemented scalable automated event infrastructure utilizing Kubernetes on Google Cloud Platform supporting over 5000 simultaneous players with personally assigned challenge machines. Held events for multiple worldwide conferences and companies including HackerOne, BSidesBoston and GrimmCon.

StewieOS qithub.com/calebstewart/stewieos

Creator x86 Assembly, C

Demonstrated expertise in low-level software and hardware programming. Designed and implemented POSIX-like kernel for the x86 family of processors. Full multitasking support. Custom device drivers for common hardware as well as implementations of common userland utilities.

Education

U.S. Coast Guard Academy

New London, CT

B.S. In Electrical Engineering

Jun 2012 - May 2016

January 22, 2021 Caleb Stewart · Résumé 2